A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 83), 1961-1991; 1970-1982; 1.9; 90.59 Cubic Feet; 224 letter-size document boxes, 10 legal-size document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, 1 half-legal document box, and 1 15-11.5 oversized document box
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - University Development, UD
      - University of Bahia - Oysterculture, 1976-1982 (Box 210, Folder 1423)
        Folder 1423 contains Evaluation
      - University of Bahia - Oysterculture: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 211, Folder 1424-1425)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Fundación para la Educación Superior (FES) - Donation of Equipment, 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 211, Folder 1426)
    - Fundación para la Educación Superior (FES) - Rural Development, 1973-1982 (Box 211, Folder 1427-1430)
    - Fundación para la Educación Superior (FES) - Rural Development (Evaluation), 1976 (Box 211, Folder 1431)
    - Fundación para la Educación Superior (FES) - Rural Development: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 212, Folder 1432)
    - Fundación para la Educación Superior (FES) - Rural Well-being, 1979-1982 (Box 212, Folder 1433)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, A
      - Universidad del Valle - Health Care, 1968-1980 (Box 212, Folder 1434-1438, Box 213, Folder 1439-1443, Box 214, Folder 1444-1446)
      - Universidad del Valle - Health Care (Evaluation), 1976, 1983 (Box 214, Folder 1447)
      - Universidad del Valle - Health Care: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 214, Folder 1448-1450, Box 215, Folder 1451-1453)
      - Universidad del Valle - Mental Health, 1978-1982, 1984 (Box 215, Folder 1454)
        Folder 1454 contains Evaluation
      - Universidad del Valle - Mental Health: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 215, Folder 1455)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Lobo A., Mario, 1976-1981 (Box 215, Folder 1456)
  - Mexico, 323
    - Colegio de México - Economic Demography, 1979, 1981-1982 (Box 216, Folder 1457)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - National School of Agriculture - Rural Development Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 216, Folder 1458)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Ortega M., Enrique Ismael, 1977-1980 (Box 216, Folder 1459)
        Second fellowship
      - Ortiz F., Guillermo, 1977-1981 (Box 216, Folder 1460)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, S
      - Colegio de México - International Review Group, 1975-1982 (Box 216, Folder 1461-1463, Box 217, Folder 1464-1467)
      - Colegio de México - International Review Group (Evaluation), 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 218, Folder 1468)
      - Colegio de México - International Review Group: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 218, Folder 1469-1475, Box 219, Folder 1476-1481, Box 220, Folder 1482-1483)
  - Dominican Republic, 335
    - Dominican Republic - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Asociación para el Desarrollo, Inc. - Development Program, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 220, Folder 1484)
        Folder 1484 contains Evaluation
  - Venezuela, 339
    - Venezuelan Federation of Private Foundations - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 220, Folder 1485)
      Federacion Venezolana de Fundaciones Privadas
    - Venezuelan Federation of Private Foundations - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 220, Folder 1486, Box 221, Folder 1487)
  - England, 401
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Hinton, Barry Thomas, 1978-1982 (Box 221, Folder 1488)
    - England - Schistosomiasis, W
      - London School of Hygiene - Data Bank, 1977-1982 (Box 221, Folder 1489)
      - London School of Hygiene - Data Bank (Evaluation), 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 221, Folder 1490)
      - London School of Hygiene - Schistosomiasis Vaccine (I), 1973-1974, 1976, 1978, 1981 (Box 221, Folder 1491)
      - London School of Hygiene - Schistosomiasis Vaccine (II), 1972-1981 (Box 221, Folder 1492-1493, Box 222, Folder 1494)
      - London School of Hygiene - Schistosomiasis Vaccine (Evaluation), 1976, 1978, 1980, 1983 (Box 222, Folder 1495)
      - London School of Hygiene - Schistosomiasis Vaccine: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 222, Folder 1496)
  - Scotland, 405
    - Scotland - Medical Sciences, A
      - University of Edinburgh - Epidemiology Conference, 1980-1983, 1987 (Box 222, Folder 1497)
  - Australia, 410
    - Australian National University - African Family Project, 1979-1981 (Box 222, Folder 1498)
  - Canada, 427
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, A
      - Geographic Medicine - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 222, Folder 1499)
        Folder 1499 contains Evaluation
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - McGill University - Nitrogen Fixation, 1977-1982 (Box 222, Folder 1500-1501, Box 223, Folder 1502)
      - McGill University - Nitrogen Fixation (Evaluation), 1978, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 223, Folder 1503)
  - Grenada/Windward Islands, 455
    - Grenada/Windward Islands - Schistosomiasis, W
      - St. Lucia - Consultants, 1981 (Box 223, Folder 1504)
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Davis, Andrew), 1971-1979, 1981 (Box 223, Folder 1505)
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Gilles, Herbert), 1971-1972, 1981 (Box 223, Folder 1506)
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Mahmoud, Adel A. F.), 1981 (Box 223, Folder 1507)
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Webbe, Gerald), 1968-1979, 1981 (Box 223, Folder 1508)
      - Saint Lucia- Donation of Equipment, 1970-1982 (Box 223, Folder 1509)
  - India, 464
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Social Sciences (Gilpatric, Chadbourne), 1967-1972, 1983 (Box 223, Folder 1510)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Deolalikar, Anil B., 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 224, Folder 1511)
      - Deolalikar, Anil B.: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 224, Folder 1512)
  - Malaysia, 473
    - Malaysia - Humanities and Arts, R
      - National University of Malaysia - International Association of Historians of Asia (IAHA), 1979-1982, 1984 (Box 224, Folder 1513)
        Folder 1513 contains Evaluation
      - National University of Malaysia - International Association of Historians of Asia (IAHA): Supplementary Material, undated (Box 224, Folder 1514-1515, Box 225, Folder 1516)
  - France, 500
    - France - Medical Sciences, A
      - Hommel, Marcel, 1978-1983 (Box 226, Folder 1521)
        Folder 1521 contains Evaluation
      - Institut Pasteur - Modabber, Farrokh Z., 1979-1982, 1984 (Box 226, Folder 1522)
        Folder 1522 contains Evaluation
        Pasteur Institute
  - Asia, 600
    - Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Downy Mildew, 1975-1981 (Box 226, Folder 1523-1524)
      - Downy Mildew: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 226, Folder 1525)
  - China, 601
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Gu, Zhiping, 1979-1981 (Box 226, Folder 1526)
      - Wang, Nai Gong, 1979-1982 (Box 227, Folder 1527)
      - Zhuang, Lin-Zhi, 1979-1982 (Box 227, Folder 1528)
    - China - Schistosomiasis, W
      - Shanghai First Medical College, 1980-1983 (Box 227, Folder 1529)
        Folder 1529 contains Evaluation
  - Japan, 609
    - Tokyo University - Fisheries and Pollution, 1978-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 227, Folder 1530)
      Folder 1530 contains Evaluation
    - Tokyo University of Mercantile Marine - Shipping Policies in the North Pacific, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 227, Folder 1531)
      Folder 1531 contains Evaluation
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Bae, In-Ha, 1979-1983, 1985 (Box 227, Folder 1532-1534)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, A
      - Mahidol University - Institute for Population and Social Research, 1972-1973, 1975-1982 (Box 228, Folder 1535)
      - Mahidol University - Institute for Population and Social Research (Evaluation), 1976 (Box 228, Folder 1536)
      - Mahidol University - Institute for Population and Social Research: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 228, Folder 1537-1539)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Downy Mildew, 1979-1983 (Box 228, Folder 1540)
      - Kasetsart University, 1963, 1965-1974, 1979 (Box 228, Folder 1541, Box 229, Folder 1542-1543)
      - Kasetsart University: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 229, Folder 1544-1548)
      - Mahidol University - Basic Sciences, 1970-1982 (Box 230, Folder 1549-1551)
      - Mahidol University - Basic Sciences (Evaluation), 1975-1978 (Box 230, Folder 1552)
      - Mahidol University - Basic Sciences: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 230, Folder 1553-1554, Box 231, Folder 1555)
      - Mahidol University - Postdoctoral Training, 1973-1980, 1983 (Box 231, Folder 1556)
      - Mahidol University - Postdoctoral Training (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 231, Folder 1557)
      - University of Medical Sciences - Basic Sciences, 1965-1969, 1973 (Box 231, Folder 1558-1560, Box 232, Folder 1561-1565)
      - University of Medical Sciences - Basic Sciences: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 232, Folder 1566)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Akwut Thasanasongshan, 1978-1982 (Box 233, Folder 1567)
      - Sathit Vannasaeng, 1980-1981 (Box 233, Folder 1568)
      - Sming Kaojarern, 1978-1981 (Box 233, Folder 1569)
      - Vichien Petpisit, 1975-1980 (Box 233, Folder 1570)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Djawanai, Stephanus (Steve), 1974-1980 (Box 233, Folder 1571-1572)
      - Sudjarwadi, Mr., 1979-1981 (Box 234, Folder 1573)
      - Sugeng Yuwono Mardihusodo, 1979-1981 (Box 234, Folder 1574)
    - Indonesia - University Development, UD
      - Gadjah Mada University - Peanuts, 1977-1982 (Box 234, Folder 1575)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Peanuts (Evaluation), 1977-1979 (Box 234, Folder 1576)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Peanuts: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 234, Folder 1577)
  - Poland, 789
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Balakier, Hanna Jolanta, 1980-1981 (Box 234, Folder 1578)
  - Sweden, 800
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, A
      - Karolinska Institutet - Diarrhoeal Diseases, 1977-1981 (Box 234, Folder 1579)
      - Karolinska Institutet - Diarrhoeal Diseases (Evaluation), 1978, 1981-1983 (Box 234, Folder 1580)
  - Turkey, 805
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Şenel, Atila Hüseyin, 1978-1981 (Box 235, Folder 1581)
      - Tezel, Yahya Sezai, 1978-1983 (Box 235, Folder 1582-1583)
  - Egypt, 812
    - Egypt - Medical Sciences, A
      - Cairo University - Liver Pathology, 1979-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 235, Folder 1584)
  - Israel, 825
    - Israel - Schistosomiasis, W
      - Hebrew University, 1977-1982 (Box 235, Folder 1585-1587)
      - Hebrew University (Evaluation), 1978, 1983 (Box 235, Folder 1588)
  - Lebanon, 833
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Alahaydoian, Eugene-Kevork, 1975-1982 (Box 236, Folder 1589-1590)
  - General Program and Policy, 900
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Financial Administration - Corporate Responsibility, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 1591)
      "Review of Corporate Responsibility Issues"
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 84), 1963-1984; 1.10; 102.51 Cubic Feet 78 record storage boxes
  Files transferred to RAC by the Rockefeller Foundation, 1984.
  - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center, 105
    - Yates, Michael James, 1979-1982, 1985, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - International Livestock Centre for Africa, 113
    - Grandin, Barbara E., 1979-1982, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - African Conflicts - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Conference title: The Global Dimension of African Conflicts: East/West Considerations and Regional Dispute Settlement
    - African Leaders - Conference, 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
      Folder 5 contains Evaluation
      Conference title: African Cultural and Intellectual Leaders and the Development of the New African Nations
    - African Leaders - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
    - American Universities Field Staff - Islamic Conference, 1980-1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Conference title: Islam, Communalism, and Modern Nationalism
    - American Universities Field Staff - Islamic Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Bacillus Thuringiensis - Conference, 1978, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Conference title: International Cooperative Group on the Spectrum of Activity of Bacillus Thuringienses
    - Black Women in Development - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Conference title: Black Women as Partners in Development
    - Changing Nature of Governance - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Clinical Epidemiology - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
      Conference title: Teaching Clinicians Epidemiology: Problems and Prospects
    - Clinical Epidemiology - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Diplomatic Techniques - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Conference title: The Transformation of Diplomatic Techniques in the 20th Century
    - Diplomatic Techniques - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Doctor's Practice Size/Visit Frequency - Conferences, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
      Conferences title: Research in Primary Care: Encounter Records and the Denominator (two conferences ran concurrently)
    - Doctor's Practice Size/Visit Frequency - Conferences: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Exchange Rates - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Conference title: Exchange Rate Theory and Practice
    - Feminism and Kinship Theory - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Foreign Languages and International Studies - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Conference title: International Council for Educational Development/European Cultural Foundation Seminar on Foreign Languages and International Studies
    - Franco-American Relations - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Health of Populations - Conference, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
      Folder 27 contains Evaluation
      Conference title: Health of Populations: Changing Perspectives
    - Health Sciences Educational Institutions - Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
      Conference title: Community-Oriented Educational Institutions for Health Sciences
    - Helsinki Watch - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 31, Box 6, Folder 32)
      Conference title: International Citizens Helsinki Watch Conference
    - Hunger and History - Conference, 1981-1983, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
      Conference title: Hunger and History: The Impact of Changing Food Production and Consumption Patterns on Society
    - INPUT - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      Conference title: International Public Television Screening Conference
    - International Affirmative Action - Conference, 1981-1984, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 36-37)
      Conference title: International Conference on Affirmative Action
    - International Terrorism - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Conference title: The Protection of Diplomatic Premises
    - Kettering Foundation - Dartmouth Conference, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      Conference title: Consultative Meeting of the United States and Soviet Leadership of the Dartmouth Conference
    - Labor Market and Education in East Africa - Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 40-42)
      Conference title: The Consequences of Educational Expansion in Kenya and Tanzania
    - Labor Market and Education in East Africa - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 7, Folder 43-44, Box R2117, Folder 45)
    - Local Institutions in National Development - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      Conference title: Local Institutions in National Development: Strategies and Consequences of Local-National Linkages in the Industrial Democracies
    - Management Institutes Working Group - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2117, Folder 47)
      Conference title: Third International Conference - Management Institute Working Group on Social Development
    - Natural Resources - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2117, Folder 48)
      Conference title: Risks and Returns in Large-Scale National Resources Projects
    - Parasitology: A Global Perspective - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R2117, Folder 49-50)
    - Poverty in the Future - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2117, Folder 51)
      Conference title: Global Poverty: Cost in Resources
    - Radio and Film Propaganda in World War II - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      Conference title: Film and Radio Propaganda in World War II: A Global Perspective
    - Rationality - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      Conference title: Rationality and Its Limitations
    - Regional Development in Europe - Conference, 1981-1983, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      Conference title: Regional Development in Eastern and Western Europe
    - Scholars - Arndt, Heinz Wolfgang, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      Unable to accept residency - did not go
    - Scholars - Baker, W. Claude, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Scholars - Bann, Stephen, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Scholars - Bergsma, William, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Scholars - Bloom, Samuel W., 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Scholars - Blumenthal, Michael C., 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Scholars - Bose, Nemai Sadhan, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Scholars - Broe, Mary Lynn, 1981-1983, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Scholars - Brooks, Alexander D., 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Scholars - Cohen, Charles Desmond, 1980, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Scholars - Cooke, Jacob E., 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Scholars - Danielson, Michael N., 1981-1982, 1986, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 66-67)
      Joint residency with Ruşen Keleş
    - Scholars - de Oliveira, Jocy, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 68-69)
    - Scholars - Dobash, Rebecca Emerson and Russell P., 1980-1982, 1984, 1992, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Scholars - Donaldson, Scott, 1981-1982, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Scholars - Farouk, Abdullah, 1980-1982, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Scholars - Feldman, Shai, 1980-1983, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Scholars - Froom, Jack, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Scholars - Fusfeld, Daniel R., 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Scholars - Halbrecht, Isac, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Scholars - Harrison, John F. C., 1978, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Scholars - Hollingsworth, J. Rogers, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Scholars - Hopkins, Jack W., 1980-1983, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Scholars - Hussain, Farooq, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Scholars - Inkeles, Alex, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Scholars - Jackson, Elmore, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Scholars - Jackson, William T. H., 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 83)
      Scholar unable to accept residency
    - Scholars - Kaagan, Stephen S., 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Scholars - Kadish, Sanford H., 1976-1978, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Scholars - Kay, Ulysses, 1979, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Scholars - Keeley, Edmund L., 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Scholars - Kekes, John, 1980-1982, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Scholars - Kern, Edith, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Scholars - Koch, Arthur L., 1981-1982, 1991, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 90-91)
    - Scholars - Kuehl, Warren F., 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Scholars - LaBarre, Weston, 1980-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Scholars - Lehman, Warren W., 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Scholars - Liehm, Mira, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Scholars - Lowenthal, Richard, 1977-1978, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Scholars - Lowrance, William W., 1979, 1981-1983, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Scholars - Luebke, Frederick C., 1981-1982, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Scholars - Luria, Salvador E., 1981-1984, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Scholars - MacAndrews, B. Colin, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Scholars - McLean, Hugh J., 1979-1982, 1985, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Scholars - Mandel, Irwin D., 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Scholars - Marsden, Philip Davis, 1981-1983, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Scholars - Mergen, Franҫois, 1981-1983, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Scholars - Meyer, Leonard B., 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Scholars - Morgan, Lael, 1980-1982, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Scholars - Mueller, Lavonne M., 1981-1983, 1985, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 107)
      Joint residency with Julia Miles
    - Scholars - Nelson, Raymond J., 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - Scholars - Nevius, Blake, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - Scholars - Nevo, Ruth, 1981-1982, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Scholars - Osagie, Eghosa, 1981-1982, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 111-112)
    - Scholars - Person, Clayton, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - Scholars - Philip, Cynthia Owen, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - Scholars - Price, Nancy, 1980-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - Scholars - Rahul, Ram, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - Scholars - Resh, Vincent H., 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - Scholars - Riesenberg, Peter, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - Scholars - Rochell, Carlton C., 1981-1983, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - Scholars - Rooke, Patricia J., 1980-1983, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 120)
      Joint residency with Rudolph L. Schnell
    - Scholars - Rosen, Jerome, 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 121-122)
    - Scholars - Rosen, Lawrence, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - Scholars - Schachter, Oscar, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - Scholars - Scherer, Klaus R., 1979, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - Scholars - Schorr, Alan L., 1980-1982, 1986, 1992, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - Scholars - Schulz, Muriel, 1981-1983, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 127)
      Joint residency with Ruth Engel-Wodak
    - Scholars - Schwabe, Calvin W., 1980-1982, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - Scholars - Sequeira, Luis, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - Scholars - Shevrin, Aliza Phyllis, 1981-1984, 1986, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - Scholars - Simpson, Louis, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - Scholars - Sivaraksa, Sulak, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - Scholars - Smith, Audrey D., 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - Scholars - Tan, Edita A., 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - Scholars - Treadgold, Donald W., 1981-1982, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Scholars - Valenstein, Elliot S., 1981-1982, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - Scholars - Valenta, Jiri, 1981-1983, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 137)
    - Scholars - von Wright, Johan, 1978, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 138)
    - Scholars - Wolters, Oliver W., 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - Scholars - Wood, Ronald K. S., 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    - Trypanotolerant Cattle in Africa - Conference, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 141-142)
      Folder 141 contains Evaluation
      Conference title: Trypanotolerant Cattle in Africa
    - Trypanotolerant Cattle in Africa - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 17, Folder 143-144)
    - Urbanization and the Arab World - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 145)
      Conference title: Urbanization and Social Change in the Arab World
    - Utility of Force in International Security - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 146)
      Conference title: The Utility of Force in International Security